Eugene Buinouski

Middle DevOps Engineer

CONTACT INFO

Eugene.Buinouski@outlook.com

in Linkedin.com/in/eugene-buinouski

? Tbilisi, Georgia

EDUCATION

Belarusian State University

Radiophysics

SPOKEN LANGUAGES LEVELS

Russian: Native English: B1-B2

PROFILE

DevOps Engineer with 5+ years of experience in providing maintenance and support for different systems and services, automation of any administrative processes, ensuring system security, fixing security threats, developing CI/CD according GitOps concept, developing python scripts for automation, troubleshooting of environment, advising development teams on the implementation of CI/CD pipelines. Looking for a DevOps job. I can start on June 1st.

EXPERIENCE

Elinext DevOps Engineer

Sep. 2022 - Jun. 2024 Migration to GCP, developing CI/CD pipelines according GitOps concept, Tbilisi, Georgia maintenance, developing python scripts for automation, troubleshooting of environment, docker, pipeline issues, consulting development teams on implementation of CI/CD pipelines, developing and implementing Ansible

> playbooks, security consulting, creation and mentoring cloud technology training.

Used frameworks and technologies:

AWS, GCP, Azure, Python, Docker, Docker-Compose, K8s, Ansible, Jenkins, Gitlab CI/CD, GitHub Actions

Nov. 2018 - Nov. 2021 Minsk, Belarus

Forbase

Organization of backups: sites, IIS settings, various directories,

configurations and virtual machine data. Up-to-date system and firmware support, high availability support. Monitoring and notification of: system, equipment, availability, integrity and safety of backups. System configuration, services and roles. Prevention of critical events.

Troubleshooting. Infrastructure planning and implementation. Automation of

administrative processes.

System Administrator

Used frameworks and technologies:

Windows Server, MS SQL, AWS (EC2, S3), Dell PowerEdge/PowerVault,

Synology NAS, Ipswitch WhatsUp Gold

Forbase System Administrator

Feb. 2017 - Nov. 2017 Internship. Minsk, Belarus

Used frameworks and technologies:

Windows Server, MS SQL, Synology NAS, Ipswitch WhatsUp Gold

PROJECTS

Elinext **Security consult**

Feb. 2023 - Jun. 2024 Security consult

Responsibilities:

Consulting and configuring security solutions.

Elinext Elinext Cloud Training Oct. 2023 - Jun. 2024 Internal cloud technology training

Responsibilities:

Creating and mentoring AWS cloud technology training.

Elinext Sat.io

Jun. 2023 - Oct. 2023 Satellite managing project.

Responsibilities:

Implementing CI/CD pipelines, advising development teams on the implementation of CI/CD pipelines, resolving issues of containerization.

Elinext Elinext Gateway

Mar. 2023 - Jun. 2023 Internal corporate network.

Responsibilities:

Developing and implementing Ansible playbooks for automated server

configuration.

Elinext Broadcom DX

Sep. 2022 - Feb. 2023 Monitoring and analysis application.

Responsibilities:

Migration to GCP, developing CI/CD, maintenance, developing python scripts for automation.

Marketing G2

Oct. 2018 - Nov. 2021 Marketing solution for social media

Forbase

Safetypay Nov. 2018 - Nov. 2021 Solution for payment methods

Forbase

Marketing G2 Feb. 2017 - Nov. 2017 Marketing solution for social media

SKILLS

AWS EC2 / Route 53 / S3 / VPC / Beanstalk / ECS / ECR / EKS / RDS /

DevTools / SNS / Cloud Formation / Cloud Watch

GCP Compute / GKE / Storage

CONTAINER TOOLS

Docker / Docker-Compose / Swarm

DEVOPS TOOLS

GitLab CI/CD / GitHub Actions / Jenkins / Ansible / Git / K8s

LINUX

WINDOWS

CentOS / RHEL / Fedora / Debian / Ubuntu / Networking (iptables, L2TP, **SERVER** WireGuard, etc.)

AD DC / GPO / DNS / DHCP / IIS / Hyper-V / DFS / Failover cluster /

SERVER WSUS

VIRTUAL Hyper-V / VMware(vSphere)

TOOLS

STORAGE

Synology NAS / Dell PowerEdge / Dell PowerVault

MONITORING Ipswich WhatsUp Gold / Zabbix **SCRIPTING** Python / Bash / PowerShell

OTHERS DELL (OME, OMSA, iDRAC) / Network Security / GitOps

PERSONALITY

Experimenting with new technologies and frameworks, continuous learning, resolving the most difficult problems, choosing the most appropriate technologies, flexible and organized.

HOBBIES

Programming, radio electronics, CTF.